20 minutes until the incident.
Well, are you prepared?
I got this.
When you go looking for the murderer, you'll find him hiding in the bathroom.
That'll be your best chance to unmask him.
Hey, Liu.
This time, trust me to take the lead.
What? Why should I?
When the killer called, his message sounded like a response.
Right?
I'll be there, as promised.
Okay, so hear me out.
What if I talked to him here, and that call was for me?
Hold on. You're saying that our present is the result of what you're about to do on her body?
That's right. I changed the timeline right now.
Things are starting to add up.
So what are you planning?
Figure out his M.O., give him some hints as to who we are, and make him play by our rules.
I'll take the message sent at 10 a.m. as a hint.
Killers like him are meticulous.
They can't stand being provoked or bested.
So, after he falls into our hands, we've got the creep.
And how exactly do you propose we trap him?
The motion sensor doorbell inside our store.
Guess who?
A guest has arrived.
Look who I brought.
We'll put it in the darkroom with a new voice.
You're pretty punctual.
The moment he enters?
Now I get it.
You weren't in here messing around earlier.
You were prepping.
Well, is that a proof I hear in your voice?
Cause that is impressive.
Just one problem.
Even if we catch the person who called us.
Where's our proof?
We'll need hard evidence he's the culprit.
Yeah, that's the most exciting part.
And the most dangerous.
It didn't take too long to realize
Something has changed in the back of my mind
Your eyes
There ain't nowhere left to hide behind
Time no longer flew like it was
When the flash froze everything before
Without you
I don't know if I could take this road
And I'm about to lose my mind
Every minute that I die back in time
Every single existence rewinds
Something secretive hidden inside your eyes
All mine
All the hottest and the smiles never faded
I know you'll be by my side when we make it
Come back from the times
Back in time
Talk back in time
Let's go.
I bet you're surprised. I was expecting you. I've seen what you want to do here, but I can't let that happen. I've got a proposition. Let's play a game. I'll send you a clue. You'll get it at 10 a.m.
Where's my phone?
Tomorrow at this time, find the real me.
Interesting. If I win, will you promise to be my new friend?
Leave this girl alone, and I won't call the cops, okay?
I've locked him inside.
Great. The game's...
...over.
So it really is you. How intriguing.
Is killing innocent people intriguing to you, too?
Innocent?
I only harm those who deserve it.
I only felt that.
He's gone.
I've finally found my truth.
Even if we catch the person who called us, where's our proof? We'll need hard evidence he's the culprit.
Yeah, that's the most exciting part. Yeah, that's the most exciting part. And the most dangerous.
I don't recognize any of these pictures.
I went through social media accounts belonging to his victims.
Their faces will get him angry.
And give me plenty of pictures to work with in a pinch.
He's the competitive type.
This'll exploit his weak points.
Then when his guard's down, I'll go in for the win.
You only care about yourself.
How have my faces cut off in that?
Okay, how about you take it?
It's your job.
My arm is too short.
Hey, dummy.
Would you get it together, please?
Why would I repent?
I've done nothing wrong.
Your parents will kill you if you don't get married soon.
Yeah, it's not one of my priorities.
Yo, one.
Now look up at mommy.
Jeez.
At this rate, the dog will be the only man in your life.
Afterward, students should turn in their monthly papers, including committee transcripts.
Really?
This is important.
And you're sneaking photos?
Have you no respect for your peers?
Each picture here represents a life you've destroyed.
Those victims did nothing wrong!
The police are currently investigating his cause of death.
So then, it's done through clubbing.
Let me make sure my eyes weren't closed.
Hey, it turned out pretty good.
A few tweaks and I'll post it.
Don't you kids ever worry about putting so many pictures online?
Oh, she's fine.
Lighten up.
It's called sharing, like how you're always showing off a designer's sweater she bought you the second it gets cold.
That is not the same.
The only people who see that are a few women in the neighborhood.
Depriving just one person of their life destroys countless others as well!
Their friends.
Their families.
All suffered because of what you did to them!
I'm only interested in you.
Whether those others are happy or not isn't my problem.
So it is you!
Don't be so sure.
I may be the person behind all of this, but not how you imagine.
So you admit it then?
You're to blame?
I was the one who killed those people.
But why would you do that?
Oh, jealousy.
Or hatred.
Maybe anger.
Whatever.
I just cared about having a good time.
The truth is, there's nobody in this world who can catch me.
Why should I bother coming up with some kind of motive?
Wrong.
You hurt the man!
Arrest him!
Away from the door!
Right behind you!
Lioumine!
Cover the entrance!
It's over!
It's all right, you're coming with us.
Hands behind your back!
Got him!
No way he's escaping.
I'll see you very soon.
And when that time comes, don't you dare cheat again, friend.
What's so damn funny?
Stand up!
There's no use pretending.
We know you aren't paralyzed, so start walking.
Stay back, everybody.
Listen, good job catching the perpetrator, but that was incredibly dangerous.
Leave it to the police next time.
Right.
Sorry.
We only just realized he might show up here.
It was a split-second decision.
Our officers searched his properties.
Shu San San was in the garage of one of his villas.
She's not hurt, just a little shaken.
Hey, there you are!
Are you two all right?
Yeah, fine.
San San too.
Long story.
I'll explain it later.
Dang, this guy seems mature for his age.
Hey, I hoped you could help me with something.
I'm a bit stumped on him's case.
Is there any chance you could help?
Oh, come on.
Stop it with the games.
We clearly heard you admit your crimes.
There's no use denying them.
Sorry, sir.
I'm lost.
I don't remember anything.
We found the kidnapped girl in your garage, yet you still deny being the killer?
What if I told you that my friend is the one behind all this madness?
Would you believe me?
Oh, really?
You have an accomplice?
If that's the case, tell me everything you know.
And make sure you start from the very beginning.
Oh, yes.
I remember this girl quite clearly.
So that's what happened.
And I think that brings you up to speed.
Wow, didn't see that coming.
I never expected that you could be so reliable.
Well, there's something still troubling me about Liu Min, his alibi for Emma's murder.
What happened that night?
If he was in the hospital, he couldn't have killed her.
And if that's the case, then who did?
This is a surveillance photo from the bridge.
Please keep it between us.
Here.
I asked Officer Chun to send me this picture.
Figured you could look and see if there are any clues.
This Emma worked in our company's finance department.
She didn't have much experience, but still became the CFO's assistant.
Mr. Liu, what are you doing?
Let me out.
Here is fine.
I'll walk home.
Is that so?
Are you trying to run away with the money?
I suspected she made off with cash when her boss was caught.
So I wanted to scare her.
Unfortunately.
Why can't parasites like you just leave me alone?
You live pathetic lives.
Then talk crap online so you can feel better.
You'll pay.
I promise.
I'll take back everything you've stolen from me.
Then I'll kill every last one of you.
I was terrified.
I thought I'd killed her.
Then I heard someone else screaming.
I went and checked the trunk, but nobody was there.
I guess the excitement of the moment got to me.
Stick to the facts that are important, damn it.
Now tell me, how exactly did that woman end up dead?
I drove fast.
Figured I'd get her some help.
The bridge only has one camera.
I can't find anything helpful.
All I see is a girl with bad injuries.
I thought she'd turned into a zombie.
I could barely hold the steering wheel.
Then she started going crazy.
Please stop.
Let me go.
Back off.
That's how I crashed the car.
I was knocked out.
My leg is completely useless because of her.
Okay, then let me dive into the photo and check it out.
Even if you do, there's a limit to what you can alter.
How about you let me see that power in action?
It's my fault.
I changed her fate.
That's why I have to go.
I can make this right.
You worthless bitch.
I'll make you pay for this.
I'm going to murder your entire family.
Let me see.
huh that's what's in style of course they're fashionable if by fashionable you mean expensive
then yes you're right when i grow up and work in the city i'll dress you up in the nicest
clothes from head to toe you'll look great gotta brag she's working as an executive at chinda games
my kid it's twitter not chinda besides i'm just the cfo's assistant that's all hear that chief
corporate my daughter's so fancy when she was young she always told us i'll go into the city
and make a good living now look talk about follow-through huh
darling we're so proud
emma this toast is to you oh no i don't know how to drink and i'm not even sure i'd like it
it's pretty easy to pick up
yeah come on drink it drink boss insists don't disappoint him go toss it back one go drink it
drink it drink it drink it drink it drink it you got moved up show your gratitude toast with us
thanks mr ju how about another round it's a celebration to emma dearest how are you lately
don't disturb her she's fine i'm sure she's just busy
i'm trying not to annoy her that's why i've barely been texting
you
Emma!
Who, who are you?
I'm sorry.
The bad things that happened tonight are my fault.
I changed things.
I didn't listen, and I screwed everything up.
I thought replying to your mom's text as you would make everyone happier.
You were the one who sent that message?
How's that possible?
Who are you?
A time traveler.
I can enter the past through photographs.
I came here to try and make up for my mistakes.
If that's really true, then is there any way you could possibly help me go back to the very beginning?
I just... I'll just start over.
Um, sir? Why are there two datasets?
Cause... comparing the numbers, it's obvious one's doctored and looks fraudulent.
Smart girl. You're thorough and learn fast.
What you lack is real-world experience.
You see, in business, sometimes numbers need to be finessed a bit.
But we're talking false accounts.
If someone found out, you'd...
I'd what?
No one's getting hurt.
Liu Min's father cut him off financially a long time ago.
So he asked me to siphon some funds from dear old dad who'll never miss them.
How could I...
I'm doing him a favor.
And getting a kickback.
It's all good.
And besides, it's a family matter and no one else's.
You know, you've been working so hard recently.
Why don't you take this bonus?
Save up some money.
Maybe buy a place in the city.
You could even move your family here.
If I could go back in time and change things, I'd say no to the dirty money.
And I wouldn't let my boss harass me.
Trust me.
Oh my god, it's a second chance.
I've known it all the way.
I have light in every way.
Because the truth always turns you away.
I've experienced many lives.
And in each one, there's been regret.
You only care about expanding.
The food no longer matters to you anymore.
And this shop is no longer mine.
It's too much.
I can't stand on it.
Pinky promise.
Dodo, I'm so sorry, my son. Please come back to us.
Every time I dive, no matter how hard I try, there's no guarantee of a perfect ending.
Perfect ending.
Listen, there's no good way for me to fix the past for you.
But I can help your future. It doesn't have to end here.
You're wrong. I have nothing left.
I've learned some things from the people whose lives I've inhabited.
Some of them persevere for love.
Oh, yeah! I've come to marry you!
I still walked away.
Lean in.
Others need to get lost in order to find themselves.
Welcome home.
Don't be afraid.
Your mama's right here to keep you safe.
I've seen what it means to be a parent and live with loss.
So I'll keep looking for a decade or more. I swear, I won't stop.
And experience the joy of a family being reunited.
For most people...
It's worth the wait.
I believe everyone has a reason to keep on living.
I don't know.
Though at times we may find ourselves in darkness...
I've seen through the night I will keep in mind
To live so that I can find
The paths where I took all the pain
Eventually, we need people who shine their light on us.
I've known it all the way.
The paths are going to be a better place.
I have known it all the way.
I've known it all the way.
When I look at the path,
What's the deal? Has he told you anything?
He keeps saying some friend of his is to blame,
claims he's a pawn!
Pawn!
Could he suffer from schizophrenia?
This friend could just be a hallucination.
Can't be.
We've conferred with his doctors.
He's mentally sound.
Yeah, but didn't those doctors also say he was paralyzed?
Definitely didn't seem that way at the studio.
My friend, come quickly.
Help me kill these annoying insects, please.
How?
Death's a node that can't be changed.
Hm? What's going on?
You seem tense.
You once said, nothing is absolute.
So it's true. There was a witness after all. Interesting.
Wait, what did you just say?
What if the Amin was a puppet?
We need good pictures. That way, others might want to join us.
Sure thing, Captain. I'll do the best I can.
So it's true. There was a witness after all. Interesting.
Wait, what did you just say?
What if the Amin was a puppet?
We need good pictures. That way, others might want to join us.
Sure thing, Captain. I'll do the best I can.
I can barely see while wearing these dumb glasses.
My son was paralyzed in a car accident.
How could he be out there hurting people? Explain that to me!
That means...
You're another one of his friends, eh?
You can possess people too.
Mama!
What the hell?
Hey!
Chowling!
Chowling?
This is your punishment for not playing fairly.
Who the hell are you?
Now then, I look forward to the rest of our game.
You should really stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
You should really stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
Really stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
Yeah.
Who are you?
Who?
Don't you die on me.
I'm on me.
Just begun.
Who are you?
Who?
Don't you die on me.
I'm on me.
Just begun.
Who are you?
Who?
Don't you die on me.
I'm on me.
Just begun.